The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives one boy who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination helped him become a magic knight.
And despite the many challenges he faces,
he aims for the top and refuses to give up.
Rich or poor, royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove that to the whole world
and to become the next Wizard King.
Asta and some of the other Black Bulls were gathered up by Marileona,
who escorted them to the Yoltem Volcano
to increase their abilities alongside the Crimson Lion Kings.
I'm gonna get there first!
No, me! No, me!
Flame magic!
Viral flames!
Inside the treacherous volcano,
Asta and friends discovered a mysterious dungeon.
This ought to be interesting.
Gah!
That was incredible!
Leopold, who considers himself to be Asta's rival,
showed great strength at battle prowess when the group was attacked.
Soon I shall master that spell and become stronger than you!
Then I'll just have to get stronger than you!
Thus, their training came to an end.
Or so they thought.
Where were you?
She's actually here?
Where are we going now?
I wish you safe travels, my dear friend.
The two of you have been selected to take care of an urgent matter of utmost importance.
You should consider it an honor.
You should consider it as a meaningful message.
That do you care personally?
Have you ever seen Chandasko?
You should know .
That was a coincidence.
какая Kyuamana, exclaimed Square.
Thank you.
Even though this is true, even from inatteir后,
I am so scared of the sophomore year,
but I believe this true future will be changed
during this time.
So Bakhtочку,
of course,
I believe that thehatgnais be turned out
on full chain over the age of cooks
Even if something has been eating form,
if something has married a bloodline,
theha intermittency the case,
This voice, your voice, my voice, which is out now
I call you
Our future millimeter will be tremendous
You miss us, realise the happy story
Let's go!
Truth is my dream
Now hurry and take a seat so we can begin.
Hang on, I don't even know where we are.
At my home, of course.
I've brought you to the Vermillion residence.
Mimosa and her brother are here.
And Captain Foygolion, too.
I see that you've been summoned as well, Asta.
I don't know if I'd call it summoned.
More like dragged here against our will.
You're as unsightly as ever.
And now you're a fugitive.
Even so, I have to admit.
Despite how it happened, there was a touch of beauty to your recent exploits.
Uh, thank you?
Believe it or not, that was my idiot big brother's idea of a compliment.
Is anyone gonna tell us what we're doing here?
I don't actually know, but look.
What's the matter with the captain?
I have no idea.
But whatever it is, it's serious.
Yeah, no kidding.
Maybe we're here because they need to give us special orders for going to battle with the Spade Kingdom.
I could see that.
Enough musing!
We have assembled you all here today for a very important meeting.
I need you to understand that whatever happens at this table has the potential to alter the course of the entire kingdom's destiny.
And I must ask you never to speak of it outside this room.
Sounds like a top secret mission.
Now then, let us begin!
Hey, I know that old lady!
Sorry, but I don't think I'm familiar.
She's a nun at the church in Neon.
I wonder what brings her here, though.
The purpose of this gathering is to celebrate Ms. Teresa's service to the sisterhood.
She's been with them for 15 years.
What?
I don't understand.
Didn't you guys just say this meeting could affect the whole kingdom's future?
Children are the future.
And Ms. Teresa takes care of a group of children.
I'm sorry, but I really don't see how I could have been any more clear than that.
I got a couple ideas, but hey, you're the boss.
Why exactly weren't we supposed to tell anybody else about this?
It's not as though it's some horrible secret.
There simply isn't any reason to tell anyone else about it.
Ms. Teresa hates the spotlight, so we can't make this flashy.
This is the worst secret mission ever!
Well, it is too flashy.
I don't want all of this fanfare.
Can't a poor old woman have some peace?
So basically, we're just here to throw her a party?
Any particular reason you're hosting this?
Back when we were small children, in addition to being a member of the Magic Knights,
Ms. Teresa was also responsible for educating my sister and me.
Oh, that's right! I think I remember you telling me about that before, sister!
Heaven help me, you haven't changed much except for your heads getting bigger.
Mero and Little Fuego.
Mero? Little Fuego?
After she finished tutoring us and left the Magic Knights, she became a sister.
And she's been with the church for 15 years as of today.
Right, ma'am?
I also heard about how violently you fought to protect everyone during the kidnapping incident that occurred in Neon.
Oh, yeah! You were awesome!
Especially for a granny!
Which is why we have designated this day to be a time of celebration!
We're here to honor Sister Teresa's lifetime of accomplishments!
And since we needed more hosts than just the two of us, we brought you along.
Okay, I think I see what this is all about.
Yeah, you want us to help throw her a super fun party!
We can do that. Certainly!
Simply beautiful!
Not your looks, obviously, because you're a hideous hag, but your spirit is simply gorgeous!
I'm learning to comprehend that non-physical form of beauty.
But of course, my Immaculate Being still outshines all the rest.
I know my brother's a grown man, but do you think you could educate him too?
He's an idiot.
Wait a second.
Why isn't Leo here?
It's a party for somebody who's really important to his siblings.
Under normal circumstances, I'd have summoned him here.
However, he asked me to let him use this time for some extra training.
So I was happy to oblige.
That's a good reason.
He's got the right idea.
Too bad you two aren't smart enough to realize what a waste this is.
It's only for today, ma'am.
Please try to have fun.
Oh, wow! Looks good!
We hope you enjoy it, Miss Teresa.
Oh.
I really don't care for big, fancy meals like this.
Perhaps it's because I've been living outside of the royal capital for so long now.
This is exactly why I almost declined your request.
Then again.
Look at the food!
Yay!
I can't wait to eat!
You generously offered to feed the little ones as well, and it would have been selfish of me to refuse that.
Hey, Marie. Nice to see you again.
Hi, Asta.
Thanks for saving me before.
You want to eat our lunch together?
Sure.
Hey, wait.
I know that key.
Asta!
Don't you want some food?
Oh.
Of course I do.
Everybody get in line, okay?
Okay!
Yay!
Here you go. That ought to be enough to get you started.
Thank you so much, Asta.
What's this about?
You may have fooled everyone else here, but it takes a lot more than a clever disguise to fool me.
Ghosh, my boy.
Shut it, old lady.
I suppose you must have had a transformation wizard change your appearance to make you look like a child.
There's someone on your squad with that skill.
I remember.
I went to the church to visit Marie, but then I heard there was a party at House Vermillion.
That's why I'm here.
Do you have some kind of problem with that, you stupid old geezer?
I see you're still as disrespectful as ever.
You and I both know you're only allowed to see Marie once every month.
You've got no regard for the rules.
It's downright shameful.
I'm just sneaking a peek during a party that we both happen to be attending, so it doesn't count.
I'm sorry to bring the fun to a halt.
Oh, what? You mean the party's over already?
No, not exactly.
Then what's the problem?
I demand that each and every one of you demonstrate your best party trick for Sister Teresa's entertainment.
What?
Now then, which one of you would like to go first?
He wants us to do party tricks?
Like juggling and things like that?
Oh, man. I hope someone explains what a party trick is.
I'm sorry. Little Fuego was never very good with words.
I do wish he would explain himself better.
I'm not interested in tricks.
I'd like you to entertain the children.
Oh, that's easy.
Leave it to me. I'm great with kids.
Let's get started.
Good thing I'm here. Ever since the day I was born, my infallible good looks have provided an endless spectacle for the masses who clamor to behold.
Considering your entire existence is a party trick, this ought to be the easiest thing you've ever done.
Just try not to break any nails, Mr. Perfect.
I don't think I know any party tricks.
Trust me, it wasn't.
This reminds me of Lady Ossiere.
In times like this, she'd always be the first one to step up.
Anytime there was a banquet, she'd do some interesting little thing to impress us.
I have one!
That's wonderful, Noelle! I can't wait to see it!
Knock our socks off! I believe in you!
I'm about to put on a show like only royalty can.
Ta-da!
This is impressive, right?
Well, if that doesn't amaze you, then nothing will.
You're amazing! Don't do that!
I can probably whip up something.
Pathetic. I could entertain Marie way better than any of those clowns can.
You shut your mouth, Gauche.
If you want my take on it, disguising yourself as a child just so you can breathe the same air as your little sister makes you the biggest clown in the room.
Who said I wanted your take, huh?
That's what he meant by party tricks! I know what to do!
Hey, Noelle, could you pass me a couple of plates?
Uh, sure.
Ta-da!
I'm not done yet!
Master's so talented!
He got the biggest reaction. Not bad, I guess.
Oh, my. Such a bizarre routine.
Though, there's a certain flair to how garish it is.
Thank you all for putting on such a spectacular show for our guests.
So, what sort of trick are you going to do for me, little fuego?
I see. It appears I'm not going to get away with doing nothing.
All right. Time to use the ace up my sleeve.
Watch closely, children.
Look at these eggs.
I don't understand. What kind of trick is he going to do with those?
Does he really think he can boil them like that?
There.
Behold!
This is crazy! How do he cook each one of these eggs to a different temperature?
By carefully controlling my mana, I can prepare eggs to several varieties of doneness at the same time.
The most challenging method is what's commonly known as the hot spring style.
The yolk of the egg should be somewhat firm while the white part maintains a gelatinous texture.
Which means for this to work, I must adjust the temperature to exactly...
Nobody cares.
I beg your pardon?
You're too serious for this, brother.
Entertaining isn't one of your strong points.
I suppose not.
Give me some room. Let me show you how it's done.
The key to a proper party trick is enthusiasm.
They'll never forget this!
Yes! Now tell me, children, are you having fun?
What are they crying about?
Still painfully oblivious, aren't you?
I apologize for this disappointing display.
It's not like it really comes as a surprise to me.
After all, your personalities haven't changed in the slightest since you were children.
Could you tell us what they were like then? Maybe a funny story or something.
Show some respect, Asta.
If I had to describe them, I'd say that although they were capable, they were still a real handful.
I'll be your tutor starting today. I look forward to instructing you.
I want to do everything I can to make myself stronger, Miss Teresa.
So please give me the most extreme training possible.
You're being silly, little fuego.
It isn't possible to become strong overnight.
He was unsatisfied with the intensity of his lessons.
So he'd always sneak away and train on his own when he was supposed to be in bed.
But training too hard in childhood can affect a person's mana and development.
So I tried to get him to hold back.
Mara was always a wild child.
She never listened to me anyway, so I let her be.
And she became a mighty warrior.
I served as the tutor to this pair of troublemakers for about a decade.
At the end of my term, little fuego was 15 years old and Mara was 17.
I apologize for being such a difficult student, Miss Teresa.
You let me have lots of freedom in my formative years, which is why I'm as powerful as I am today.
So I'm very grateful to you.
Well, that's kind of you, but I was only doing my job.
You must be a great teacher.
Though I bet you they were both super good fighters even when they were little.
Oh, hardly.
Little fuego had terrible mana control.
Frankly, in his youth, the boy was a walking fire hazard.
Yeah, I remember that.
You caused tons of fires, and you cried like a baby every time.
But do you remember the time you worked yourself into a tizzy when you were eight and accidentally set your clothes on fire?
Now that you mention it, I think I do recall that.
Such fond memories, aren't they, sister?
These growing pains are to be expected for children born with extraordinary levels of mana.
But with time and practice, their ability to control their magic naturally grows in proportion to their potential.
I get it.
It makes sense that I couldn't control my mana for so long.
I was a late bloomer.
Then having poor mana control is kind of like wetting the bed.
For most kids, it's not a problem after about ten years old, but for some it keeps happening.
Sometimes even until they're thirteen or fourteen.
Yes, well put.
That's an excellent analogy.
It really is a lot like wetting the bed, huh?
Master, you jerk!
I don't even know what I did wrong!
I can hardly imagine anybody making it through childhood without picking up a few embarrassing memories along the way.
Speaking of embarrassing memories, one time, back when we were little, Fuego Leon broke a vase our family had had for generations.
I couldn't bear to see my little brother punished, so I took the blame for it.
Pardon me, dear sister. It's been many years and some of the details may have passed from your memory.
You were the one who broke that vase and I who took the blame.
Ah, you certainly sound convinced that what you're saying is true.
And it's not like it was out of character for you, right?
It was the same thing after you pilfered that magic item from Father and lost it.
You told everyone I'd taken it and they believed you.
That'll be enough out of you.
Did you make room in your memory for these trifles by forgetting about all the times you swiped food from me without permission?
Or did you think I didn't notice because I never said anything?
That never happened.
Once again, you were the family's constant food swiper and I the long-suffering victim.
I'm sorry, sister, but I can't allow you to spread these falsehoods to our guests unchallenged.
Falsehoods? You better not be calling me a liar, Fuego Leon.
Then I must insist that you recant your lie.
Don't think for a second that you're too grown up for me to beat another lesson into your fat head.
Feel free to take a shot.
What do we do, sister?
That's how siblings are. Just let them slug it out.
Although you, over there, Missy.
Uh, you mean me?
Please, throw up a quick spell to protect the kids.
I don't want them to get hurt in this malarkey.
Yeah, got it.
Take a good long look, kids, and don't let yourselves grow up to be like them.
Okay.
Two people having different versions of a childhood memory hardly seems a surprise.
I, too, protected my dear sister quite often, but it seems all those memories have escaped her.
What? When did you ever take the fall from me?
I beautified a room for her once after she made a terrible mess of it.
Man, I never would have guessed.
That's enough of your nonsense.
You won't embarrass me in front of Husta.
You, do you know how many times I had to sweep the entire house after you'd been practicing magic by throwing loose flower petals all over the floor?
Oh, come now. I'm sure it couldn't have been that many.
I've wasted so many hours of my life cleaning up after you.
Conflict is unbecoming to one as beautiful as myself, but your vile slander against me must not go unanswered.
I've already heard more than enough of your excuses, brother.
If you lack the sense to shut your mouth, then I'll do it for you.
I've never seen mimosa like this before, but there's a first time for everything.
I won't be holding myself back anymore.
Good, because I've been waiting for some entertainment.
Hey, you morons! You're gonna hurt Marie!
Whoa, where'd a ghost come from?
You weren't supposed to be here.
I won't let anybody harm my sister. Got it?
You stay out of this! It's between me and my idiot brother!
You two need to cool it! You're taking this fight way too far!
You're taking this fight way too far!
That's enough! All of you!
Whoa! She put a stop to all those fights in an instant!
Now sit
How appalling
Of course siblings fight
But that was too much by any measure
I'm terribly sorry for losing my composure
With you like that brother
I had a less than beautiful moment too
And you too
Your behavior today has been well beyond mortifying
You're in your thirties
You have no excuse to be squabbling hard enough to leather your home
We apologize most sincerely
Wait one damn second you old bag
What are you just going to stand there
Making that smug face at me
Oh there you are
I was wondering where you'd landed
You wouldn't be in trouble
If you didn't come here without permission in the first place big brother
If nothing else
The fact that your sister turned out so much smarter than you is comforting
And you two did excellent work as well
Thank you so much for looking out for the children
Now it's time we get on our way
Miss Teresa leaving so soon
I've had plenty of your company
I apologize again for how we've conducted ourselves
But please let us make it up to you by hosting you again
I get the feeling you haven't done much entertaining
Was it really that obvious?
Indeed
But it's still nice to know that the two of you are so eager to have me here
So let's see
My hundredth year of service will be in 85 years
If you can fit me into your schedule
That she leopard
She's really tough, huh?
Seriously
She could probably take out a devil on her own
You don't live to be an old bag like me without picking up a few tricks
My hundredth year of service
I'll raise it and if i'm fading about time
I keep you literally
No matter where I could
Do what you need
I change the blah
It's only that you can leave
I die from China
Thank you.
Don't forget it. Don't forget it.
Don't forget it.
That's my heart.
If you're here, I'm not alone.
The one who has my heart, my mind, and soul.
Stupid Osta! What do you mean the one who has my heart? I'm royalty, you know. Jeez.
...